Hello Hello friends Welcome to Saath Ka Stock
Friends, today's video is going to be very
important friends today we
will talk about ICICI Bank in today's video
friends ICICI Bank has a
good past record in such a bank friends
friends we will
discuss all this what label is coming out next label is this
tiger coming out on this first of all
friends we will
explain it to you by doing technical pro of the chart by drawing lines and you have all the beats in it meanwhile
we are going to discuss so friends do
you stay with this video till the end so that
you have understood it well and now
you should learn to do technical analysis well
see friends the market is also moving and the
current price
of ICC right now
friends see our meaning is
770 and this is today's wish friends 1.5
that is different and we were raising a question of one percent
here you are getting pillar by pillar here
and here friends let us talk about this thing
friends if we get maximum return here  But if
we talk about it, then look here,
you will see the maximum return, 5696 point 6
3, that the return here, you will see the return, see the
growth of your company, see how Kosli has given
you a good growth return here,
and here we
would like to show you one more thing, friends, here you
see, see this forecasting, forecasting,
friends, definitely we can
show our brother, see here 98%
analysis of have suggested that you were stuck in the
district, friends, 98% means that
its number is very high, friends, that is,
more, that means, it is doing well at the bank level,
friends, wine labels, friends, then
you should invest in it
and by investing in it
you can generate a good profit,
and the thing that we will see, friends, there is not much in it, first
look at our entry point,
this is our entry point, your
Mario, good time to consider h2o, note
airplane mode on, and the second one will show you
any problem, see the bank's share
dividend, friends, friends, is very low, and here
it is telling friends that now it  It is a good
ton but look friends we can see through the chart
see how
it has generated a good profit as requested
so friends we have to pay
attention to it see the return here
5696 point seventy percent here
we have the return so a little friends it was a
Gy so it will not take much time
because in whatever video of mine
friends I will tell you a little about the
company and this company is
friends, see a little about ours but
this is the financial of private bank
ICICI Bank and what is the last decision
friends this is a very good company of Play Store
and its Raghavendra in NSC will be at
8 here and if we
talk about market cap then 8 here it is
a company of 4 lakh 84 thousand 9 hundred 96 crores
so this is just a little bit in it I will spend
more time taking loan friends and on this we
go to the chart
friends this is on our channel so please
subscribe to our channel and do
not forget to hit the bell icon so friends let
us go to the chart  But let's go friends, take out some
time and definitely learn to make chaat and
I show increasing chaat in every video, so
this match, I made tea and brought it, the
line went from here, from there I
taught you how to make chaat online, the
current in front of you, so the line here has gone down
friends, this is the line,
friends, that is why I have drawn the first test in between, so from
here ma'am
I am going to take the chart from 2018 till now, just a little bit, just have the
courage, so from here we will see
friends, when it was placed in 2018, friends, whenever it was
placed all time high, at that time its
price was around 375 376
friends here and after that the
resistance friends which was 375
375, look here for a little 1 second, this is
our all time high lines, let's
try to decorate it a little nicely and after that friends, what
we placed is about two and a half circles,
after placing half circle low, there is more price,
friends, when three and a half vicious criminals backed up,
friends, you can see the affair here
that it will give you about 550, from two and a half
As if you take this record, friends,
here on this record, on the dry dry superintendent
price, you have got the price,
put it around 380, so you
get to see the price only 500 550, after that
friends, the price that you are
seeing here, the
time you
made here, how much did you earn here, it is
not 547, sir, around 500 and the term is made,
after that the drive here also, last year
this is for Abir, it is full of quality
and in this type of stock, you will get this very good question,
your first theme, very
good introduction and see from there friends, when
you got this price, you got about two and a half
subscribers and see friends, here you have been
here for a long time,
friends, this support, so we will
understand through the channel, so you should take a little
more time,
see this, I have drawn a line for you,
friends, this is it and this, which here,
see, after Assistant Assistant Assistant,
this is our
Ghagra
and to do it,
you should subscribe from here
and friends, it was done here
Resistant, you must
write a line below the line that you have drawn,
friends, this has been spent a lot of time, let me tell you, in this
you can see from the middle of the real upper, I
love September, and in the way of September, it is
almost certain that from the middle of September, three months
four here, till September, friends, this
stock here and like friends, look, this is
our president, president, friends,
this is
our three
subscribe and here, friends, let me draw a line from
here, this is
this line,
I will move the chart a little here
and see friends, from here, whatever
you recorded, it reached an all-
time high at 380, you should put it
around 680, when it almost reached around 680, friends, it will
request a little, it will increase in
inches, when it is all-time high, which
was placed before Djokovic, this is
our assistant length here, which
crossed it, so look at this,
this president means to
take support, first of all, you support, now
when the price goes up, this becomes
our line, we start working from the support,
look here, we took the support,
support  After taking the support,
friends, you have seen all the time that here,
like it broke one and a half here, it
went till here, then this killing element of the back is the
price, friends, and it has broken, it has
broken and for about three-four weeks,
friends, this price has become an assistant
system for you, that is, friends, this is
our clear and pregnant and this is
our separate and confirmed view, so from here,
friends, it was very good for us, so from
here, one, you can
increase the respiration, you can make a plus portion, from
here you will almost see,
friends, let's go around seven hundred,
you can see 707 and secondly,
friends, see this confirmation here and see this, friends, see,
I have stopped this timeline,
see from here, how can you see, it is taking support, taking support
to the base, still it has
swelled, that is, friends, this is our off
trend, that is, our price is also
going towards April, see, this happened and there will be a trend,
friends, and this is our don't friend,
so look at the price, you see this often and
this is our etc.  Look at the shadow and
look at the train and look at the ad here, how
nice you can see it in the police form here, here
like you
make a press with Sanjay, then your stoploss
friends, this resistance
line of yours has become our support line, it is a support
line, so the skin will remain above it
friends, the strike
comes from below it, it comes on a close basis, so the
meaning of saying close basis, friends, let me tell
you that again this is formed by doing a close way cigarette, if
you approach it below, then this is
our close basis, this is our
stoploss, sometimes friends, what happens is that
this stock comes down, but by keeping it
above this line every day, my
Star Plus here gets cooked by hitting, in this way,
if you keep a stoploss on close basis, then
almost 90% of your stoploss will
pass, that is,
do backtesting, backstage friends, the
biggest thing I will tell you is that now until
you do not practice on your own in the market, you have
seen how to make a chaat like this, the
line cries, where is the support, where is the
resistance, I am full friends  I
want to work in a prices organization and friends, this is what I
want to tell you friends, you should
work on this fry section and use
this indicator under this program, keep the
movie constipation on, movie 19
and friends, if we talk about any stock, then it should at
least come above the moving average of others,
friends, if the movie is below that then
friends, do not buy it and do not invest in it
and its stop loss is as I have told you
and in the target friends, I will give
you a target from here like this line which I am
telling you, friends,
this is the line, touch this line from here and
keep the CM line here, here
you are here and the chart should be made a little
false
and you will get it till here,
yes, it will be touched in it and you will see
this thing till here, almost friends, this
wrist of ours, this deposit tigers, friends, our
price is coming out approximately note 7,
then it is coming out normal and this is how much
price we run approximately
271 271 here friends, this time
from here you will get a president, so friends, here you are getting
This is the thing, we should subscribe here 9
so that you will get to see it here,
friends, know till today,
this makes you fashionable, so this from here and
this is the first
and here you can see
that you have it and you will get the second information
friends, another opposite chapter of your subscribe,
this drink water is installed friends,
this is our pivot point friends, I
respect you a lot, this is
my first assistant account of business, this is a
little friends,
subscribe a little friends, look a little in crossing it,
spend time here, see, for
almost a month, friends
try to cross the president here, friends,
like this
subscribe friends, you will get it
here friends,
see this friends, friends, I was here, see the
chart, friends, it was not very simple,
now see friends, I have done it a little here, now see friends, see the
entire chart here, it is
ready, so from here,
see for yourself, from here you can see whether a
buy level is being formed or not, from
here you boil it and move on and the first target
of that in this there are notes and in this 9  It is
showing from but you will get
to see this target of thousand within the next six months, friends, it is
not certain that it will reach there
but this is the stock market, you can guess through technical, through fundamental,
friends, our work keeps going on on it, so friends,
we hope that if you
liked this video, then please do like, like, like,
friends, if you are on our channel, then
please do
not forget to subscribe to our channel, we will meet
friends in this video, thank you for
watching the video, tell me why, thank you,
thank you.